어떤 말도 들리질 않아
내 심장 소리뿐
서둘러 날 고쳐보지만
I can’t live without you
내 맘은 불길처럼
걷잡을 수가 없어
이런 나를 내버려둬
이 밤을 가로질러
너에게 가고 있어
늘 그래왔던 것처럼
알잖아 너와 나
애써 외면하지 마
We will be beautiful
And we’ll stay together for all time
이제 더 이상 참고 싶지 않아
Give you all of the love in my heart
이제 온 세상이 다 내 것 같아
Give you
Ay ay ay ay ay ay ay ay
Give you all of the love in my heart
Give you
Ay ay ay ay ay ay ay ay
Give you all of the love in my heart
Thinking ’bout you every day and night
우리 마음은 마치 Stars align
춤을 추게 해 매일매일
Get lost in the twilight
You belong with me forever
Let’s go whenever
Don’t you know I’m down bad
Oh babe 너 땜에 꼬여
Can’t control my mind
보여줘 If your love’s true
Shout it out, I’m so into you
알잖아 너와 나
애써 외면하지 마
We will be beautiful
And we’ll stay together for all time
이제 더 이상 참고 싶지 않아
Give you all of the love in my heart
이제 온 세상이 다 내 것 같아
Give you
Ay ay ay ay ay ay ay ay
Give you all of the love in my heart
Give you
Ay ay ay ay ay ay ay ay
Give you all of the love in my heart
You and I
밤하늘 아래 등을 맞대고 앉아
You have my back and I’m glad for that
별빛처럼 아름다워
이제 더 이상 참고 싶지 않아
Give you all of the love in my heart
이제 온 세상이 다 내 것 같아
Give you
Ay ay ay ay ay ay ay ay
Give you all of the love in my heart
Give you
Ay ay ay ay ay ay ay ay
Give you all of the love in my heart